

ABOUT ME

A diligent and enthusiastic frontend focused fullstack developer with 1 year of working experience.

As an individual I am friendly and approachable person with experience of multiple cultures that can adapt in many different social groups.

My main passion lays within the IT domain and always curious to learn more. Other passions includes cooking, walks in nature and games.

WEBSITE & SOCIAL LINKS

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/alexander-risteski-seiya

GitHub github.com/Kanzaki404

Portfolio

alexander-risteski-seiya.com

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH Fluent

NORTH MACEDONIAN Fluent

SWEDISH Proficient

JAPANESE Proficient

SERBO-CROATIAN

ALEXANDER RISTESKI SEIYA

Frontend Developer

Alexander.Risteski@protonmail.com ■

073 755 20 22

Västanvindsgatan 6A, Göteborg

WORK EXPERIENCE

Precisely

Göteborg May 2022 - June 2022

Stratsys

Göteborg

Sep 2021 - Mar 2022

Ericsson

Göteborg Oct 2020 - May 2021

Hello World!

Växjö Mar 2018 - Jun 2018

Frontend Developer

- Improving & fixing features on client side using React.
- · Agile processes with tools such as Jira, Git and Google cloud patform.

Jr Developer Trainee (fullstack)

- Creating and updating micro-frontends in vue3.
- · Writing unit tests with jest.
- Implementing accessibility support for screen readers and tested using NVDA program.
- Agile processes with tools such as Jira, Git and Azure.
- Learning .Net framework and engaging in bug fixes

Frontend Developer Intern

- Creation of wireframe, mockup and implementation of frontend as well as backend with database.
- Thesis work at Ericsson was conducted through a task to create a mobile version of an already existing web/ browser app using React Native

Programming Instructor

My task included teaching programming concepts using a program called Scratch and engage the students by building simple games.

EDUCATION

EC Utbildning

Göteborg Sep 2019 - May 2021

Linnaeus University

Växiö

Sep 2016 - Jun 2019

Frontend Developer

- Main topics were fundamentals of web development, front end frameworks, UX/UI, Agile work and surface level backend/database courses.
- The education includes 6 month period of internship. with an aim to gain work experience upon graduation.

Network Security Program

- Areas of focus were network/server administration, network security and cryptography.
- The program also included courses within software development such as data structures, software testing and database theories.

SKILLS

Frontend

HTML/CSS JavaScript TypeScript React lest Vue2&3 React Native Redux

Backend

Node.JS ASP.Net MVC ——

Databases

MongoDB SQL UX/UI Figma Photoshop

Work Methodologies

Agile Scrum Kanban